语法简述：即使在复杂句中，也要重读名词，除非有对比。所有你一直想知道、
Grammar, in a nutshell, even in complex sentences, stress the noun unless there's
却又不敢问的语法知识都在这里。英语是一种按时间顺序展开的语言。
contrast. Everything you ever wanted to know about grammar but were afraid to use.
我们特别在意事情发生的时间，这体现在
English is a chronological language. We just love to know when something happened,
英语动词时态的范围和深度上。
and this is indicated by the range and depth of our verb tenses. I had already
正如你可能在语法课上学过的，
seen it by the time she brought it in. As you probably learned in your grammar
正如你可能在语法课上学过，过去完成时表示过去某个动作之前的动作，
studies, the past perfect is an action in the past before a separate action in the
不是所有的语言都能做到这一点。例如，日本人对
past. Phew! Not all languages do this. For example, Japanese is fairly casual about
事情发生的时间并不那么严格；但日语是层级语言，所以非常重要的是，
when things happened, but being a hierarchical language, it's very important
这取决于两个人之间的关系。上级和
to know what relationship the two people involved had. A high-level person with a
下级、两个同级、一个男人和一个女人，都会体现在日语语法中。
low-level one, two peers, a man and a woman, all these things show up in
语法上说，英语是民主的；令人困惑的是，
Japanese grammar. Grammatically speaking, English is democratic. The confusing part
在英语中，动词时态非常重要，
is that in English, the verb tenses are very important, but instead of putting
我们不是把它们放在句子的峰顶，而是把它们全部丢进低谷。
them up on the peaks of a sentence, we throw them all deep down in the valleys.
因此，像 Dogs eat bones 和 Dogs'll eat bones 这样语调很强的两个句子，
Therefore, two sentences with strong intonations, such as dogs eat bones and
the dogs will have eaten the bones，听起来非常相似。为什么？因为说
the dogs will have eaten the bones, sound amazingly similar. Why? Because it takes
两个句子所需时间相同，因为它们有相同数量的重音。
the same amount of time to say both sentences since they have the same number
在这些句子中，原来的三个词和节奏保持不变。
of stresses. The three original words and the rhythm stay the same in these
但随着加入更多重读词，意思会改变。冠词和动词时态变化
sentences, but the meaning changes as you add more stressed words. Articles and verb
通常不重读。现在，让我们看看这在
tense changes are usually not stressed. Now, let's see how this works in the
接下来的练习。
exercises that follow.